{
    "subject": "Jacques_Feyder",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Fran\u00e7oise_Rosay",
    "human_readable": "Jacques Feyder is married to Fran\u00e7oise Rosay.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887073040008545,
            "question": "Is Fran\u00e7oise Rosay married to Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9634577631950378,
            "question": "Who is Jacques Feyder married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.915221095085144,
            "question": "To whom is Fran\u00e7oise Rosay married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9076626300811768,
            "question": "What can you infer about the relationship between Jacques Feyder and Fran\u00e7oise Rosay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9007691144943237,
            "question": "Who is Fran\u00e7oise Rosay married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8611016869544983,
            "question": "What is the name of Jacques Feyder's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8476085662841797,
            "question": "What is the name of Jacques Feyder's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7778247594833374,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marital status of Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12112545222043991,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in a marriage relationship according to the given information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11970069259405136,
            "question": "Is there a marriage relationship described in the information provided?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jacques Feyder is married to Fran\u00e7oise Rosay.",
            "html": "yago_8586_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the individuals involved in a marriage relationship according to the given information?",
            "html": "yago_8586_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the marital status of Jacques Feyder?",
            "html": "yago_8586_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jacques Feyder's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_8586_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8586_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Jacques Feyder is married to Fran\u00e7oise Rosay. In multiple files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8586/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8586/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt), it is mentioned that Fran\u00e7oise Rosay was married to Jacques Feyder."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Jacques Feyder is married to Fran\u00e7oise Rosay.\" Multiple texts, such as those found in files 69.txt and 26.txt, explicitly mention their marital relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}